Guide to the Sylvère Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive MSS.221
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Manuscripts from the Semiotext(e) Archive
  - Subseries A: Manuscripts
    - Baudrillard, Jean "UBU" or "Artaud and Pataphysics", c.1995 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Baudrillard, Jean (Revisions for unknown ms), c.1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "From Radical Incertitude, or Thought as Imposter", 1997 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Towards the Vanishing Point of Art" (Original text for Whitney lecture), c.1997 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Oublier Artaud" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), c.1999 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "Dropping out of History" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "L'euphorie sous perfusion", undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "L'extase de la communication", undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "La gauche divine", undated (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - [Baudrillard, Jean] "Metaphysique de l'otage", undated (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Baudrillard, Jean "USA '80", undated (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Behenna, [Veralynn] "May 20, 1992", c.1992 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Bellamy, David (Untitled ms), c.1992 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Bellour, Raymond (Interview with Deleuze and Guattari- Unpublished), 1972 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Betensky, Carolyn and Robert Callahan "Rituals of Transparency", undated (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Bifo (Untitled proofs), 1993 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Blumenthal, Henry "Mobius Love", undated (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - [Boltanski, Luc] "Entretien avec Pierre Morhange", undated (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Bouillon, Victor J. "Bio/Closure", undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Broderick, David "Rose Forrest Rose", c.1990 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - Brown, Martin "Vanishing Return", undated (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Brown, Trisha (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Brownstein, Michael "A Touch", 1991 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Breuer, Lee "The Shaggy Dog Animation" (with S.L. marginalia), 1978 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Breuer, Lee "Book of Love", undated (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Burroughs, William "The Limits of Control", undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Carlin, John "Nietzsche Interview", undated (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Carter, Michael "Remarks on the 1st Five Year Plan", undated (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 46)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 47)
    - Chabert, Elizabeth Allen "Transforming Impact: The Shock Experience in Dada and Surrealist Poetry" (dissertation), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 48)
    - Charyn, Jerome (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), c.1984 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Cixous, Helene "Reponses tant bien que mal" (transl. [Roz Morris]), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 50)
    - Cobey, Patricia "I Have Often Dreamed of Arriving Alone in a Strange Country", undated (Box 23, Folder 51)
    - Cohen, Josh "Late Mailer, Baudrillard, and the Technological Disintegration of the Public Sphere", undated (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Cohen, Sande "Notes on K. Ross' Review of Premises", undated (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Crevel, Rene "Difficult Death" (transl. David Rattray), c.1984 (Box 23, Folder 54)
    - Daitch, Susan "Incunabula", 1985 (Box 23, Folder 55)
    - Dali, Salvador "Oui 1 & 2" (transl. Yvonne Shafir), undated (Box 23, Folder 56)
    - Dean, Kenneth and Brian Massumi "The Elimination of Strength", undated (Box 23, Folder 57)
    - Debord, Guy "La societe du spectacle" (English film script), 2005 (Box 23, Folder 58)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Presence and Function of the Spider Madness", [1973] (Box 23, Folder 59)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Nietzsche's Philosophy" (transl. James Leigh, Desert Islands), 2002 (Box 23, Folder 60)
    - Deleuze, Gilles "Two Regimes of Madness" (final transl. Robert Hardwick Weston), undated (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Diaz, George "On Crime Scenes", 1983-6 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Diaz, George "On Crime Scenes" (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Dick, Leslie "Death by Drowning" (extract), 1991 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Dobbs, Bob "Phatic Communication with Bob Dobbs", 1997 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Dubuffet, Jean "Anticultural Positions", 1951 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Duden, Anne and Clea Wallis "Why Don't We Laugh When We Tickle Ourselves", undated (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - [Durbin, Shannon] "Nine West Girls", undated (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Duschke, Rudi "La bombe genetique", undated (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Elber, Mark "Lost and Found" and other poems, undated (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Emerling, Susan "Julie", 1990 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Flanagan, Bob "The Pain Journal" (Proofs), 1990 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Flanagan, Bob "The Pain Journal" (Proofs), 1990 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Fletcher, Jim (Various), undated (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Foreman, Richard "Perspectives of Real Time", undated (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Foreman, Richard (On Stein), undated (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Foucault, Michel "Discourse and Truth" (Original for "Fearless Speech"), 1983 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Foucault, Michel "Fearless Speech" (Proof), 1998 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Foucault, Michel "On Infantile Sexuality", undated (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Franklin, Jean "The Speech of Power" (transl. Phil Beitchman), c.1980 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - Gallo, Ruben "Losing One's Head: Julia Kristeva and Decapitation", undated (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Garnet, Eldon "The Garden of Failure: Writing Brooke Shields", c.1995 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Garnet, Eldon "Allegory", undated (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Garrett, Daniel "The Cultural Politics Discussion Group, Gestures Toward an American Utopia", 1993 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - Gente, Peter and Heidi Paris et. al "Atalanta Interviews", c.1984 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Georges, Margaret "Dada's Unclean Cuisine", 1987 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Gilbert-Lemonte, Roger (Various poems transl. David Rattray), undated (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Gilbert-Rolfe, Jeremy "Nietzschean Critique and the Hegelian Commodity", 1997 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Gilbert-Rolfe, Jeremy "Beauty and the Contemporary Sublime", undated (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Godzich, Wlad "University Seminar on the Theory of Literature", 1974 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Guattari, Felix (Transcript of an unpublished lecture), 1970s (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Guattari, Felix w/ Lotringer, Leclaire, Clement at Reid Hall "Le Phallus, la Sainte-Vierge, et les Martiens", 1973 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Guattari, Felix "Et pourquoi pas une pragmatique generative et transformationnelle?", 1974 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Guattari, Felix "Pour une [micro]-politque du desir" (Reid Hall lecture), c.1974 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Guattari, Felix (Textes de colloque), 1980s (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Guattari, Felix "Le sac de Chez Lancel" (Unpublished), 1980 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Guattari, Felix "Chaosophy" (1st versions), c.1985 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Guattari, Felix "Crac en plan pas un pli" (Fiction, original typescript), 1986 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Guattari, Felix (Fictions), 1986 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - Guattari, Felix "Genet Regained", 1986 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Guattari, Felix and Gilles Deleuze (Interview typescript), undated (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Guattari, Felix "Pour un regroupement democratique et revolutionnaire" (Unpublished), undated (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Guyotat, Pierre "Eden, Eden, Eden" (transl. Graham Fox), 1984 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Hariu, Ichiro "Hyu Shiroo" (w/ transl. by Joseph Love), undated (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Hass, Amira "Reporting from Ramallah", 2002-3 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Hass, Amira "Reporting from Ramallah", 2002-3 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Hell, Richard "The Voidoid" (w/ bio and photo), 1973, 1990s (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Herbich, Barbara "Affliction, Redemption, and the Written Word in Duras and Antelme", undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Hochschild, Rosemary "Bar Tapes" (Excerpts), 1979 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Hotswede, Eric (Untitled ms), undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Indiana, Gary (Various mss), c.1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Irigaray, Luce (Book, title unknown), 1999 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Jackson, Susanne (Various poems), undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Jacoby, Roberto "With the Whole Body", undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Janowitz, Tama "Some Omitted Text for a Semiotic Analysis", undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Jaussely, Jean-Jacques and Madeleine Mitton "Mot a mot", undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Jordan, Ken "Speaking with David Rattray", 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Joxe, Alain (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Joxe, Alain "Empire of Chaos", 2001 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Joxe, Alain and Jaffe (Documents for Joxe's book), undated (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Joxe, Alain (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Joxe, Alain "Petites guerres cruelles et paix en panne", undated (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Kaplan, Alice "Taste Wars: American Professions of French Culture", 1985 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Katz, Vincent "Pearl" (+ copy of "New York Hello!"), 1992 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Kaufman, Julie (On "Le degre zero de l'ecriture"), undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Kelley, Mike "Hollywood" and "Baby", undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Kelley, Mike (Various mss), undated (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Kelsey, John and Jim Fletcher "Special Implants 3-9", undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Kiel, Mark "Barthes/Autumn/Me", undated (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - King, Kenneth (Various mss), undated (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Klein, Jason "Chorus for a Psalm", c.1980 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Kops, Hannah "The Glass Menagerie- A Media Spectacle", undated (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Krakauer, Daniel "Eight Plays", undated (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Krakauer, Daniel "The Portable Abyss", undated (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", 1987 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", 1988 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving", c.1988 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Ann Rower "Sadness at Leaving" (Film proposal, correspondence), c.1989 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Fate, The Tribe, & 1000 Modern Coincidences", c.1990 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1994 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick" (Sylvere Lotringer's Dick Journal), c.1994 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick" (Print-out of original letter exchange between Chris and Sylvere), c.1994 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1996 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "I Love Dick", c.1996 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia", c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Early draft), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Gavin Brice, close to last draft), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Gavin Brice, outtakes), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Letter to Lloyd Phillips, unsent, Mexico), 1999 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Letters), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Notes, review for Paragon House), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Notes, starvation, biochem, Warren Niodik conversation), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Outtakes), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Paul Thek diaries), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Aliens and Anorexia" (Transcript sans soleil), c.1999 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Torpor", c.2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris (Willa Cather notes and draft, Horicon Studio), 2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Exterminating Angel", 2007 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Arnette the Absolute", undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Baby", undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action", undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Disparate Action/Desperate Action" (Notes), undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris (Interview), undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Readings from the Diaries of Hugo Ball", undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Singles", undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris "Terrorists in Love", undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - (DEACCESSIONED) Kraus, Chris and Barbara Barg "What Are Women Up To?", undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Kristeva, Julia "The Necessity of Revolt", c.1996 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Kristeva, Julia "Artaud entre psychose et revolte" (From Artaud conference at MoMA, may be unpublished), undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Lacan, Jacques "The Pure Subject of the Signified" (Original typescript), 1970s (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Lachman, Ed "Framed" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Lazarin, Michael "All Political Economy is Libidinal", undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Lebel, Jean-Jacques "Ginsberg/Flash/Ginsberg" (Edition privee reservee aux amis), 1997 (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Lefebre, Henri "Le possible et l'impossible", undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Levine, Eliba "Trapped", 1976 (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Lindenman, Catherine "Gustave Flaubert: The Origins of Aesthetics" (Table of contents), undated (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Lindsay, Arto (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Lisker, Roy "Poli-sexuality and Cosmology", 1979 (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Lofton, Saab (Untitled ms), undated (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Loselle, Andrea "Cultural Tourism in 20th Century French Literature", 1996 (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Loselle, Andrea "Cultural Tourism in 20th Century French Literature", 1996 (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Ludd, Deran "Sick Burn Cut", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Ludd, Deran "Sick Burn Cut", 1991 (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Lyotard, Jean-Francois "Freud According to Cezanne", c.1973 (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - McCormick, Brian "Phantom Quest" and "On Being Grue", 1998 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - McCormick, Brian "Which-way Data, Mama?", "Malevich" and "Transcendence is Sky", 1998, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - McGrath, Patrick "Black Hand of the Raj", undated (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Mailer, Norman (Interview for High Times), c.1979 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Menon, Becca "Chronic Solutions", undated (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Thurston "How I Became One of the Invisible", 2001 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Morra, Louis (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Morris, Rosalind "Interview with Helene Cixous", 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Mortimer, Alan "Codex 151", 1997 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Moshenberg, Daniel (Untitled ms), undated (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Mueller, Cookie (Untitled ms), undated (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Muller, Heiner "How German Is It?" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Muller, Heiner (Interviews), undated (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Muller, Heiner "Post-Wall Berlin" (Interview), undated (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Muller, Heiner "The Walls of History" (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Musil, Robert "The Blackbird" (transl. Peter Wortsman), 1983 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Yoga of Anger", 1982 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Myles, Eileen (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), 1988 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Real Drive", 1988 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Myles, Eileen "The Real Drive: Poems 1981-1989", c.1989 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Myles, Eileen "Not Me" (Proofs), 1990 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Myles, Eileen "Cool for You", undated (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Myles, Eileen "Cool for You", undated (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Myles, Eileen "I Am Your President", undated (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Myles, Eileen "Poems", undated (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Myles, Eileen "Robin", "Quietude" and "Robert Mapplethorpe Picture", undated (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Myles, Eileen (Untitled ms), undated (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, w/ S.L. annotations and Negri letter), 1986 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, w/ letter from Gilles Labelle), c.1987 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, cassette transcription), c.1987 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Negri, Toni (Interview with Sylvere Lotringer, cassette #1), c.1987 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Negri, Toni "Theses", 1989 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Negri, Toni "Postmoderno", c.1990 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - Negri, Toni (Transcript of interview/trial), undated (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - Overlie, Mary (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Pell, Derek "Assassination Rhapsody", undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Peoples, David and Janet "Twelve Monkeys", 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Perez, Rolando Jr. "On An(archy) and Schizoanalysis", 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Perez, Rolando Jr. "Love and Hatred of French Theory in Capitalist America", c.2001 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Perrin, Veronique "Les bizarreries de la pudeur", undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Perry, John "Psychosis & Visionary States", 1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Cynthia "Thesis on Koons", c.1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Pickering, Shawn "Poems", undated (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Poe, Amos (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Preston, John "A Story Dedicated to Jason", undated (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Preston, John "Stop Over in Boston", "Weekend in NYC", "Mineshaft" and "Tenth Welt", undated (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Rainer, Yvonne "Journeys from Berlin/1971" (w/ S.L. notes), 1980 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Rammellzee "Ionic Treatise on Gothic Futurism", 1979 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Raskin, Jimmy "The Prologue", undated (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Rattray, David "In Nomine", c.1991 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Rattray, David "Artaud's Cane", 1992 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible", c.1992 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible", c.1992 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Rattray, David "How I Became One of the Invisible" (Proofs), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Rattray, David "The Angel" (w/ copy of interview by Ken Jordan), undated (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Rattray, David "La mort difficile- Translator's Introduction", undated (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Rattray, David "Sounds of the River Naranjana", undated (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Ray, Susan "The Adventures of Binnie the Kid", undated (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Reich, Steve (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Reilly, Nancy "An Inch of Pennies", undated (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Reilly, Nancy "A Professional High", undated (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Roche, Maurice "Compact" (transl. M. Polizzotti), undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Rogers, Benji "Letter from Palestine and Israel", 2004 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Rolnik, Suely "Beyond the Identity Principle", undated (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Romero, Jorge "The Artifice of Parody and the Parody of Artifice", undated (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Rose, Sherrie "In Semi-sickness and in So-called Health" (on Bob Flanagan), undated (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Rossi, Jeri and Duane Davis "The Cinema of Transgression", undated (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Rower, Ann "Ghost", undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Rower, Ann "[Good Night Irene, I Mean Steve]", undated (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Rower, Ann (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer, original), undated (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Rower, Ann (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Rower, Ann "Just the High Points", undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Rower, Ann "Vito in Europe", undated (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Roy, Camille "Tigerish", undated (Box 29, Drawer 1)
    - Roy, Camille (Various mss), undated (Box 29, Drawer 2)
    - Sanders, Ed "Among the Damned" (incl. layouts), late 70s (Box 29, Drawer 3)
    - Sarraute, Nathalie (Unknown ms), 1959-62 (Box 29, Drawer 4)
    - Shafir, Yvonne (Unknown ms), c.1985 (Box 29, Drawer 5)
    - Smith, Duncan "Turkey in State", 1979 (Box 29, Drawer 6)
    - Smith, Jack (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 29, Drawer 7)
    - Spampinato, Denise "Domino of the Ordinary Hyperbola", undated (Box 29, Drawer 8)
    - Stadler, Matthew "The Sex Offender", 1990 (Box 29, Drawer 9)
    - Stark, Casandra "Murderrape" and other texts, undated (Box 29, Drawer 10)
    - Strahs, J. "Higher Letters", undated (Box 29, Drawer 11)
    - Sweet, D. "Max Jacob", undated (Box 29, Drawer 12)
    - Taffu, David "Scent", undated (Box 29, Drawer 13)
    - Tillman, Lynne "The Madame Realism Complex", c.1992 (Box 29, Drawer 14)
    - Tillman, Lynne "On Eldon Garnet: A Conversation, Sylvere Lotringer with Lynne Tillman", c.1998 (Box 29, Drawer 15)
    - Tillman, Lynne "Committed", undated (Box 29, Drawer 16)
    - Tillman, Lynne "Fixing Memory", undated (Box 29, Drawer 17)
    - Torreauta, Maurizio "Interview of Ramm-Ell-Zee", undated (Box 29, Drawer 18)
    - Torreauta, Maurizio (Untitled ms), undated (Box 29, Drawer 19)
    - Trundle, Boo "The Vast Underneath", undated (Box 29, Drawer 20)
    - Trundle, Boo "Whizzy Gets Stabbed", undated (Box 29, Drawer 21)
    - Tweedie, Merylyn (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 29, Drawer 22)
    - Tweedie, Merylyn (Interview by Sylvere Lotringer), undated (Box 29, Drawer 23)
    - Violeau, Jean-Louis "L'architecture dans la critique radicale" (Proofs), 2004 (Box 29, Drawer 24)
    - Virilio, Paul and Sylvere Lotringer "La guerre pure" (Unpublished original for "Pure War"), 1982 (Box 29, Drawer 25)
    - Virilio, Paul (Additions to "Pure War"), 1997 (Box 29, Drawer 26)
    - Virilio, Paul and Sylvere Lotringer "Crepuscular Dawn", c.1997 (Box 29, Drawer 27)
    - Virilio, Paul and Sylvere Lotringer "Crepuscular Dawn" (Edited), c.1997 (Box 29, Drawer 28)